A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Washington, DC, Series O FA350
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Special Assistant to the President Declassified Materials, 1954-1956, 1969; 9; 4 Cubic Feet
  - Miscellaneous Projects, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 76, Folder 587.
  - Organization, Personnel, and Security, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 76, Folder 588.
  - Moral Rearmament, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 76, Folder 589.
  - Procedures, Equipment, and Supplies, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 76, Folder 591.
  - Foreign Economic Policy - Soviet Activities, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 77, Folder 597.
  - Foreign Economic Policy - Asia, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 78, Folder 598.
  - Militant Liberty (Action) - Book I, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 78, Folder 599.
  - Militant Liberty (Action) - Book II, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 78, Folder 600.
  - Militant Liberty (Action) - Book III, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 78, Folder 601.
  - Dynamic Democracy, April 28, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 78, Folder 602.
  - Public Opinion - Factors Relating to Four-Power Conference, June 11, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 79, Folder 605.
  - Public Opinion - Additional Factors in Western European Opinion About Foreign Ministers Conference, October 15, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 79, Folder 609.
  - Cultural Activities - Cinerama, Porgy and Bess, Soviet Union, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 80, Folder 615.
  - Cultural Activities - President's Emergency Fund, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 80, Folder 618.
  - President - NAR Correspondence to Eisenhower, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 82, Folder 625.
  - Secretary of State - NAR Correspondence to Dulles, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 82, Folder 628.
  - United States Information Agency - Policy Papers, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 82, Folder 631.
  - United States Information Agency - Publications and Soviet Propaganda Activities, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 83, Folder 632.
  - Departments and Agencies - General, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 83, Folder 634.
  - Afro-Asia - Colonialism and Neutralism - Bandung Conference, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 83, Folder 635.
  - Afro-Asia - Colonialism and Neutralism - Bandung Conference, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 84, Folder 637.
  - Africa, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 84, Folder 639.
  - Antarctica, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 84, Folder 640.
  - Europe - General, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 84, Folder 642.
  - Italy, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 84, Folder 643.
  - Afro-Asia - Colonialism and Neutralism, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 84, Folder 638.
  - Germany, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 85, Folder 644.
  - Iceland and Finland, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 85, Folder 645.
  - Near and Middle East - Policy Papers, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 85, Folder 648.
  - India - Tata Iron and Steel Company, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 85, Folder 651.
  - India - Economic Aid and General, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 85, Folder 650.
  - India - General, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 85, Folder 649.
  - South and Southeast Asia - Policy Papers (India, Philippines, Indonesia, Singapore), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 86, Folder 652.
  - South and Southeast Asia - Policy Papers (Indonesia), 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 86, Folder 653.
  - South and Southeast Asia - Overseas Chinese (Asian University), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 86, Folder 654.
  - South and Southeast Asia - General, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 86, Folder 655.
  - South and Southeast Asia - General, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 86, Folder 656.
  - Far East - China, Korea, and Formosa, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 86, Folder 657.
  - Far East - Japan, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 87, Folder 659.
  - Latin America - Policy Papers, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 87, Folder 660.
  - Latin America - Countries (Brazil), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 88, Folder 664.
  - Latin America - Countries (Chile and Guatemala), 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 88, Folder 665.
  - Soviet Union - Policy Papers, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 88, Folder 667.
  - Soviet Union - Soviet Orbit Propaganda, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 88, Folder 668.
  - Soviet Union - Exchange of Visitors (General), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 88, Folder 666.
  - Soviet Union - Exchange of Visitors (Farmers), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 669.
  - Soviet Union - Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 670.
  - Chronological Files, February 1955 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 672.
  - Chronological Files, March 1955 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 673.
  - Chronological Files, April 1955 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 674.
  - Chronological Files, May 1955 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 675.
  - Chronological Files, June 1955 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 676.
  - Chronological Files, July 1955 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 677.
  - Chronological Files, August 1955 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 678.
  - Chronological Files, September 1955 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 89, Folder 679.
  - Chronological Files, October 1955 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 90, Folder 680.
  - Chronological Files, November 1955 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 90, Folder 681.
  - Chronological Files, December 1955 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 90, Folder 682.
  - H. H. Porter and J. I. Coffey - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Materials from British Embassy, January 1956 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Non-Military Psychological Warfare, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 96, Folder 724.
  - Planning Coordination Group History, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Quantico Panels, June 1955 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    See also Subseries 7, Box 96, Folder 728.
  - White House Files, c. 1956 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Planning Drafts for Office on Defense Mobilization - Office for Free World Cooperation, May 1956 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Originals of Excised Documents from Latin American Mission (from III 4 O.8), 1969 (Box 4, Folder S1)
    See also Subseries 8 - Presidential Mission to Latin America.